[
  {
      "questionNo": "Q1.",
      "question": "Which resource is predominantly used to find synonyms and antonyms?",
      "options": [
          "Dictionary",
          "Thesaurus",
          "Word book",
          "Encyclopedia"
      ],
      "correct": 1
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q2.",
      "question": "The Thesaurus is also known as a:",
      "options": [
          "Book of synonyms",
          "Book of antonyms",
          "Dictionary of synonyms",
          "Dictionary of Antonyms"
      ],
      "correct": 2
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q3.",
      "question": "Which one do we find in a Thesaurus:",
      "options": [
          "Synonyms: Strongest, Strong, Weak matches",
          "Antonyms: Strongest, Strong, Weak opposites",
          "Both A and B",
          "None of the above"
      ],
      "correct": 2
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q4.",
      "question": "Choose the correct option: The company is in …………………… problem.",
      "options": [
          "Massive",
          "Large",
          "Magnanimous",
          "Big"
      ],
      "correct": 3
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q5.",
      "question": "Choose the strongest and weak match for the word ‘delay’.",
      "options": [
          "Jam and stall",
          "Stoppage and detention",
          "Both A and B",
          "Lag and hold up"
      ],
      "correct": 3
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q6.",
      "question": "Select the word which is closest in meaning to the given word: ADJOURN",
      "options": [
          "Hasten",
          "Halt",
          "Conceive",
          "Postpone"
      ],
      "correct": 3
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q7.",
      "question": "Select the opposite of Accurate:",
      "options": [
          "Precise",
          "Definite",
          "Brief",
          "Both A and B"
      ],
      "correct": 3
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q8.",
      "question": "Which word is NOT an antonym of ‘Congested’?",
      "options": [
          "Crowded",
          "Overfull",
          "Fulfilled",
          "Full"
      ],
      "correct": 2
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q9.",
      "question": "Which is NOT a synonym of the word ‘Mercy’?",
      "options": [
          "Benevolence",
          "Correspondence",
          "Assurance",
          "Both B and C"
      ],
      "correct": 3
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q10.",
      "question": "‘Apparition’ is a synonym of;",
      "options": [
          "Witch",
          "Spectre",
          "Notion",
          "Dream"
      ],
      "correct": 1
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q11.",
      "question": "‘Grievance’ is an antonym of:",
      "options": [
          "Delight",
          "Affliction",
          "Beef",
          "Resentment"
      ],
      "correct": 0
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q12.",
      "question": "‘Surrender’ is NOT the antonym of:",
      "options": [
          "Abdication",
          "Submission",
          "Renunciation",
          "All of the above"
      ],
      "correct": 3
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q13.",
      "question": "‘Merge’ is the antonym of",
      "options": [
          "Consolidate",
          "Disperse",
          "Fuse",
          "Incorporate"
      ],
      "correct": 1
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q14.",
      "question": "The synonym(s) of ‘cosmos’ are:",
      "options": [
          "Organisation",
          "Macrocosm",
          "Both A and B",
          "Evolution"
      ],
      "correct": 2
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q15.",
      "question": "The weak opposites of ‘brute’ are:",
      "options": [
          "Weak",
          "Humanitarian",
          "Both A and B",
          "Wicked"
      ],
      "correct": 2
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q16.",
      "question": "The strongest matches of ‘Dupe’ are:",
      "options": [
          "Patsy",
          "Sitting duck",
          "Bamboozle",
          "All of the above"
      ],
      "correct": 3
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q17.",
      "question": "The weak opposite for ‘Solitude’ could be:",
      "options": [
          "Togetherness",
          "Companionship",
          "Friendship",
          "All of the above"
      ],
      "correct": 3
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q18.",
      "question": "Which word is NOT an antonym of ‘Distraught’?",
      "options": [
          "Distressed",
          "Perturbed",
          "Agitated",
          "All of the above"
      ],
      "correct": 3
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q19.",
      "question": "Which is NOT a synonym of the word ‘Gaunt’?",
      "options": [
          "Fat",
          "Emaciated",
          "Thin",
          "Angular"
      ],
      "correct": 0
  },
  {
      "questionNo": "Q20.",
      "question": "The strongest matches for ‘Conceived’ are:",
      "options": [
          "Set up",
          "Founded",
          "Initiated",
          "All of the above"
      ],
      "correct": 3
  }
]
